<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dapp on Dev Arc</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/tags/dapp/</link><description>Recent content in dapp on Dev Arc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:28:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/tags/dapp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>03 Understanding Blockchain with ethersjs 4 Tasks of interacting with smart contract</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/03-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-interacting-with-smart-contract-3ef6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:28:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/03-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-interacting-with-smart-contract-3ef6/</guid><description>In third part of this ethers.js tutorial, we will use ethers.js to interact with smart contract.
What we do here is a little beyond the scope of learning ethers.js:
Write a ERC20 token smart contract with OpenZeppelin Deploy the smart contract to Hardhat local testnet Interact with smart contract using Ethers.js Task 1: Write ERC20 token smart contract We will write an ERC20 token smart contract using the verified and popular solidity token library OpenZeppelin.</description></item><item><title>02 Understanding Blockchain with ethersjs 4 Tasks of wallet</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/02-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-wallet-nn5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/02-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-wallet-nn5/</guid><description>Ethers.js provides functions to deal with Ethereum blockchain wallet. You can find Ethers.js documents about Wallet here.
Get a better understanding with the following tasks:
Task 1: Create wallet from mnemonic and privateKey Task 1.1 Create wallet from mnemonic 1 2 3 4 5 6 mnemonic=&amp;#39;myth like bonus scare over problem client lizard pioneer submit female collect&amp;#39; //check whether it is valid mnemonic ethers.</description></item><item><title>01 Understanding Blockchain with ethersjs 4 Tasks of Basics and Transfer</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/01-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-basics-and-transfer-5d17/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:23:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/01-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-basics-and-transfer-5d17/</guid><description>As a web3 developer, you can play with Ethereum blockchain using Ethers.js to get a deeper understanding. This 3-parts tutorial lists 12 tasks for you.
Ethers.js is a Javascript API for Ethereum blockchain which can work with Mainnet, testnet such as Ropsten, Rinkeby, local testnet, Layer 2 and sidechains.
We will use Hardhat Ethereum development environment to set up a playground as it can provide all the components we need:</description></item></channel></rss>