<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Questions on Dev</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/tags/questions/</link><description>Recent content in Questions on Dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Athul</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/tags/questions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>At what age do the students graduate from school in the city of Ember?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/at-what-age-do-the-students-graduate-from-school-in-the-city-of-ember/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/at-what-age-do-the-students-graduate-from-school-in-the-city-of-ember/</guid><description>At what age do the students graduate from school in the city of Ember? At age 12, the children of Ember graduate from school and take jobs maintaining their community.
What grade level is City of Ember? The City of Ember: The First Book of Ember
Interest LevelReading LevelReading A-ZGrades 4 – 8Grades 3 – 8W How does city ember end? At the very very end, Mrs. Murdo is walking alone.</description></item><item><title>Can you camp anywhere you want in Colorado?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/can-you-camp-anywhere-you-want-in-colorado/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/can-you-camp-anywhere-you-want-in-colorado/</guid><description>Can you camp anywhere you want in Colorado? Unless otherwise noted, camping in national forests is free, anywhere in the country. Wilderness areas in Colorado—like Mount Zirkel, Mount Evans, or Weminuche—also often have great free camping, but remember that these spaces have more regulations than National Forest or BLM land.
Where can I camp in Colorado without a reservation? 6 Glorious Campgrounds Around Denver Where No Reservation Is Required
1.</description></item><item><title>Can you find black opal in Coober Pedy?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/can-you-find-black-opal-in-coober-pedy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/can-you-find-black-opal-in-coober-pedy/</guid><description>Can you find black opal in Coober Pedy? The black opal found in Coober Pedy is considered some of the best in Australia. In 1956, the largest and most valuable opal ever found was discovered in Coober Pedy. Coober Pedy is one of the few places on earth where most of life happens underground.
What colour are the best opals? Black opal is the most prized opal and may realise prices over AUD $15,000 a carat.</description></item><item><title>Can you go on a safari in Tanzania?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/can-you-go-on-a-safari-in-tanzania/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/can-you-go-on-a-safari-in-tanzania/</guid><description>Can you go on a safari in Tanzania? There are at least 20 African countries where one can go on safari, but surveys of both tourists and expert travelers regularly rate Tanzania as the top safari destination. The country is home to two of the most well-known and amazing places for wildlife viewing – Ngorongoro Crater and Serengeti National Park.
Where are the best safaris in Tanzania? Northern Safari Circuit – the most popular Tanzania safari route comprising the Serengeti, Ngorongoro, Lake Manyara, Tarangire and Kilimanjaro.</description></item><item><title>Do people live near the Yangtze River?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/do-people-live-near-the-yangtze-river/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/do-people-live-near-the-yangtze-river/</guid><description>Do people live near the Yangtze River? People &amp;amp; Communities Today, the Yangtze region is home to more than 400 million people, or nearly one-third of China’s population. Some of China’s largest cities—Chengdu, Chongqing, Wuhan, Nanjing, and Shanghai—are all located in the plains that adjoin the banks of the Yangtze River and its tributaries in the basin.
How does the Yangtze River affect people? The 700,000-square-mile Yangtze River basin provides water, transport, and food for almost one-third of China’s 1.</description></item><item><title>Does African speak Creole?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-african-speak-creole/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-african-speak-creole/</guid><description>Does African speak Creole? Examples from Africa include Sango, a creole based on the Ngbandi language and spoken in the Central African Republic; Kinubi, based on the Arabic language and spoken in Uganda; and Kikongo-Kituba and Lingala, which are based on Kikongo-Kimanyanga and Bobangi, respectively, and are spoken in both the Democratic …
Is Creole still spoken? Today, Louisiana Creole is spoken by fewer than 10,000 people. For example, speakers of Louisiana Creole who identify as Cajuns often label their language ‘Cajun French’, though on linguistic grounds their language would be considered Louisiana Creole.</description></item><item><title>Does Alaska have different time zones?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-alaska-have-different-time-zones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-alaska-have-different-time-zones/</guid><description>Does Alaska have different time zones? Alaska consolidated to two time zones – Alaska Time and Hawaii-Aleutian Time – in 1983 to put our state capitol, Juneau, on the same time zone as the more populated Anchorage and Fairbanks (and to make doing business with companies in the Lower 48 states a little easier). …
What countries are 12 hours ahead of EST? UTC+12[edit]
Fiji. Kiribati: Gilbert Islands. Marshall Islands.</description></item><item><title>Does Diana Ross live in Arizona?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-diana-ross-live-in-arizona/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-diana-ross-live-in-arizona/</guid><description>Does Diana Ross live in Arizona? She continues to perform and splits her time between Tucson and California. R&amp;amp;B diva Diana Ross was charged with DUI in late 2002 in Tucson.
Where does Diane Ross live? Los Angeles
Ross, 73, was born at Hutzel Women’s Hospital in Detroit and now lives in Los Angeles.
Where was Diana Ross born and raised? Detroit, Michigan, United States
Diana Ross/Place of birth
How old was Diana Ross when she had her last child?</description></item><item><title>Does every country in the Middle East have an abundance of oil?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-every-country-in-the-middle-east-have-an-abundance-of-oil/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/does-every-country-in-the-middle-east-have-an-abundance-of-oil/</guid><description>Does every country in the Middle East have an abundance of oil? The Middle East’s association with oil production primarily comes from countries like Saudi Arabia, Iran, Iraq, and Kuwait. Each of these has over 100 billions of barrels in proved reserves.
Where does most of the oil in the Middle East come from? Saudi Arabia is the world’s largest oil producer and accounts for roughly 15% of global output. Iraq has increased production since the end of the Iraq War and is now the second-largest producer in the Middle East.</description></item><item><title>How are cooling towers powered?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-are-cooling-towers-powered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-are-cooling-towers-powered/</guid><description>How are cooling towers powered? As the water flows through the cooling tower, it is exposed to air, which is being pulled through the tower by the electric motor-driven fan. When the water and air meet, a small amount of water is evaporated, creating a cooling action.
Which working fluid is used in cooling tower? Heat transfer methods wet cooling towers or evaporative cooling towers operate on the principle of evaporative cooling.</description></item><item><title>How are jury duty summons selected in California?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-are-jury-duty-summons-selected-in-california/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-are-jury-duty-summons-selected-in-california/</guid><description>How are jury duty summons selected in California? In California, a pool of potential jurors is randomly selected from the local population of individuals eligible for jury duty. are not currently on a grand jury or another trial jury. are not under conservatorship. have had civil rights restored if you have been previously convicted of a felony.
Can you ignore jury summons California? A court can treat ignoring a jury summons as contempt of court, which is a criminal offense in California.</description></item><item><title>How did the governor of Arkansas try to stop black students from attending a desegregated high school?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-did-the-governor-of-arkansas-try-to-stop-black-students-from-attending-a-desegregated-high-school/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-did-the-governor-of-arkansas-try-to-stop-black-students-from-attending-a-desegregated-high-school/</guid><description>How did the governor of Arkansas try to stop black students from attending a desegregated high school? On September 4, 1957, the first day of classes at Central High, Governor Orval Faubus called in the Arkansas National Guard to block the black students’ entry into the high school. Eisenhower sent in federal troops to escort the Little Rock Nine into the school. It drew national attention to the civil rights movement.</description></item><item><title>How do you call a +44 mobile number from the UK?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-do-you-call-a-44-mobile-number-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-do-you-call-a-44-mobile-number-from-the-uk/</guid><description>How do you call a +44 mobile number from the UK? On a landline/fixed phone, dial the international access code and country code (011 44) followed by the UK number.
Does WhatsApp work in Italy? WhatsApp mobile penetration in Italy H1 2018, by month In 2018, WhatsApp was the most used chat app in Italy. However, according to data tracked by Walletsaver, the mobile penetration of WhatsApp decreased from 76.4 percent in February 2018 to 67.</description></item><item><title>How do you convert cm to cm squared?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-do-you-convert-cm-to-cm-squared/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-do-you-convert-cm-to-cm-squared/</guid><description>How do you convert cm to cm squared? In order to convert from centimeters to square centimeters, you need to multiply the width in centimeters by the length in centimeters. A – area in cm2; b – width in cm (centimeters, centimetres); l – length in cm (centimeters, centimetres).
How many square centimeters go into square inch? How many square centimeters are there in 1 square inch? There are 6.4516 square centimeters in 1 square inch.</description></item><item><title>How do you multiply feet and inches?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-do-you-multiply-feet-and-inches/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-do-you-multiply-feet-and-inches/</guid><description>How do you multiply feet and inches? Since there are 12 inches in a foot, this is how to multiply feet and inches: Convert feet-and-inches amounts to inches only. To do so, multiply the feet by 16 and add the inches….Example: Multiply 5 feet 7 inches times 4:
5*12+7 = 67 inches. 67*4 = 268 inches. 268÷12 = 22R4. Final answer: 22 feet 4 inches. How do you multiply height in inches?</description></item><item><title>How does the rule of law work in Australia?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-does-the-rule-of-law-work-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-does-the-rule-of-law-work-in-australia/</guid><description>How does the rule of law work in Australia? The rule of law restricts the powers of governments, corporations and individuals, and protects against the exercise of power without a lawful basis. The laws of Australia apply to everyone, including Government Ministers, Parliamentarians and Judges.
Who has to obey the laws in Australia? All Australians are equal under the law. No person, group or religion is above the law. Everyone, including people who hold positions of power in the Australian community, must obey Australia’s laws.</description></item><item><title>How hot was it yesterday in Chicago?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-hot-was-it-yesterday-in-chicago/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-hot-was-it-yesterday-in-chicago/</guid><description>How hot was it yesterday in Chicago? Chicago Weather History for the Previous 24 Hours
ConditionsComfortTimeTempHumidity10:53 am86 °F72%9:53 am84 °F77%8:53 am81 °F79% What is the hottest temperature ever in Chicago? 109 degrees
1, 1870, to the present — a period of about 150 years — Chicago’s highest temperature is 109 degrees, recorded on July 23, 1934, at Midway Airport. The official weather observation station for Chicago was located at the University of Chicago at that time, and on that date the high temperature was 94 degrees.</description></item><item><title>How many acres does it take to feed a cow for a year?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-acres-does-it-take-to-feed-a-cow-for-a-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-acres-does-it-take-to-feed-a-cow-for-a-year/</guid><description>How many acres does it take to feed a cow for a year? Feed. The pasture or range acreage needed for each cow is 10 to 12 acres per year.
How much forage does a cow need per day? Cows will voluntarily consume 2.0% of body weight or 24 pounds per day. The 24 pounds is based on 100% dry matter. Grass hays will often be 7 to 10% moisture. If we assume that the hay is 92% dry matter or 8% moisture, then the cows will consume about 26 pounds per day on an “as-fed basis”.</description></item><item><title>How many governors of California have there been?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-governors-of-california-have-there-been/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-governors-of-california-have-there-been/</guid><description>How many governors of California have there been? List
No.GovernorTerm in office37Gray DavisJanuary 4, 1999 – November 17, 2003 (recalled)38Arnold SchwarzeneggerNovember 17, 2003 – January 3, 2011 (term limited)39Jerry BrownJanuary 3, 2011 – January 7, 2019 (term limited)40Gavin NewsomJanuary 7, 2019 – present Who was California’s last Spanish governor? Pablo Vicente de Solá
Pablo Vicente de Solá (1761–1826) was a Spanish officer and the twelfth and last Spanish colonial governor of Alta California (1815-1822).</description></item><item><title>How many medals did China win in the 2021 Olympics?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-medals-did-china-win-in-the-2021-olympics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-medals-did-china-win-in-the-2021-olympics/</guid><description>How many medals did China win in the 2021 Olympics? Key Facts. The U.S. earned 113 medals, 39 of which are gold, 41 silver and 33 bronze. China came in second with 88 medals, 38 of which are gold, followed by the Russian Olympic Committee (71 total medals), Great Britain (65) and Japan (58).
Has China ever won the Olympics? As of 2021, with the nation’s 11th appearance at both Summer and Winter Olympics, China has won a total of 275 goal medals, making them the 5th most successful country in Olympics history, after the USA, the Soviet Union, Germany, and Great Britain….</description></item><item><title>How many square feet is 23&amp;#215;24?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-feet-is-23x24/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-feet-is-23x24/</guid><description>How many square feet is 23×24? Square footage is calculated by multiplying width by length. So if a area is 23 foot wide by 24 foot long, 23 x 24 = 552 square feet.
How many square feet does a pack of insulation cover? 10 bags/pallet is equal to 110-pieces/1065.60 sq. ft. The right insulation can save on energy and heating and cooling bills.
How much will a bag of insulation cover?</description></item><item><title>How many square feet is a 14 by 9 room?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-feet-is-a-14-by-9-room/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-feet-is-a-14-by-9-room/</guid><description>How many square feet is a 14 by 9 room? Square footage is calculated by multiplying width by length. So if a room is 14 foot wide by 9 foot long, 14 x 9 = 126 square feet.
How many square feet is 9 feet by 14 feet? Square footage is calculated by multiplying width by length. So if a room is 9 foot wide by 14 foot long, 9 x 14 = 126 square feet.</description></item><item><title>How many square make a cent?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-make-a-cent/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-make-a-cent/</guid><description>How many square make a cent? 1 cent is equivalent to 435.6 square feet.
How do you convert cents to acres? Cents to Acres Conversions To convert from cents to acres, multiply your figure by 0.01 (or divide by 100) .
What sent 1 acre? Cent is referred to as 1/100th part of an acre, i.e. 100 Cents make up one acre….Dimensions of Cent.
1 Cent0.004 Hectare100 Cents1 Acre1 Cent40.47 sq m1 Cent48.</description></item><item><title>How many square miles is the city of Detroit?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-miles-is-the-city-of-detroit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-many-square-miles-is-the-city-of-detroit/</guid><description>How many square miles is the city of Detroit? 370.1 km²
Detroit/Area
A map accompanying the article is labeled “A Sprawling City: Detroit’s downtown is compact, but the city is enormous, encompassing 139 square miles” (emphasis supplied). As it turns out, 139 square miles is not at all enormous in the context of American cities. In fact, Detroit is a bit of a runt among its peers.
What’s the population of metropolitan Detroit Michigan?</description></item><item><title>How much compost do I need for an acre of land?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-compost-do-i-need-for-an-acre-of-land/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-compost-do-i-need-for-an-acre-of-land/</guid><description>How much compost do I need for an acre of land? Common application rates of compost are typically between 1.5 and 10 tons of dry compost per acre for annual application, but rates of 50 tons of dry compost per acre are not uncommon if applied sporadically.
How many square feet does a yard of compost cover? 100 square feet
A yard of any material will cover approximately 100 square feet at 3 inches of depth.</description></item><item><title>How much does disability pay in Colorado?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-does-disability-pay-in-colorado/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-does-disability-pay-in-colorado/</guid><description>How much does disability pay in Colorado? The average SSD benefit is about $1250.00 per month in 2019, however your disability benefit could be lower or higher than this amount. The maximum disability benefit payable in Colorado or any other state through the Social Security Disability Insurance program is $2861.00.
What states offer temporary disability benefits? The states that have some type of short-term disability program are California, Hawaii, New Jersey, New York, and Rhode Island.</description></item><item><title>How much is a m2 in London?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-is-a-m2-in-london/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-is-a-m2-in-london/</guid><description>How much is a m2 in London? In London overall, the average house price is £656,495, while the average square metre of property in the city will set buyers back £8,091, the research found.
How much is a square foot in London? In London, the country’s capital, the average size home currently stands at 705 sq ft. With the average London property going for £513,997, that’s an average cost of £729 per sq ft.</description></item><item><title>How much of Colorado is urban?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-of-colorado-is-urban/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-much-of-colorado-is-urban/</guid><description>How much of Colorado is urban? Roughly 98% of the population within the entire urban corridor region is within Colorado and roughly 85% of Colorado’s population resides within the urban corridor region.
Is Denver Colorado urban or rural? Denver was the most populous city of the 18-county Front Range Urban Corridor, an oblong urban region stretching across two states with an estimated 2018 population of 4,976,781.
Is Boulder rural or urban?</description></item><item><title>How were European castles built?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-were-european-castles-built/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/how-were-european-castles-built/</guid><description>How were European castles built? Many northern European castles were originally built from earth and timber, but had their defences replaced later by stone. Early castles often exploited natural defences, lacking features such as towers and arrowslits and relying on a central keep.
What do you need to build a castle? Agree on a workable design. Source a large, and skilled, workforce. Secure the building site. Landscape the area. Lay the foundations.</description></item><item><title>In which part of the day will you find fog?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/in-which-part-of-the-day-will-you-find-fog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/in-which-part-of-the-day-will-you-find-fog/</guid><description>In which part of the day will you find fog? Answer: The part of the day when fog is most likely to be seen is at the dawn, because at that point of time temperature ranges absolutely lowest from other time of the day. Due to the condensation of water vapour and cooling down of land air fog is formed as droplets of water are formed into tiny form.
What dew point causes fog?</description></item><item><title>Is Belarus a poor country?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-belarus-a-poor-country/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-belarus-a-poor-country/</guid><description>Is Belarus a poor country? Belarus has one of the lowest poverty rates in Europe, but economic growth is anemic due to archaic state-run industries and the ending of Russian energy subsidies. Its biggest political crisis is even more of a threat. Belarus is often described as having the last Soviet-era economy.
Is Belarus a rich country? Belarus is the world’s 72nd-largest economy by GDP based on purchasing power parity (PPP), which in 2019 stood at $195 billion, or $20,900 per capita….</description></item><item><title>Is Blueberry and jamun are same?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-blueberry-and-jamun-are-same/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-blueberry-and-jamun-are-same/</guid><description>Is Blueberry and jamun are same? is that “blueberry” is an edible round berry, belonging to the cowberry group , with flared crowns at the end, that turns blue on ripening and “jamun” is synonym of jambul.
What is another name for blueberries? Blueberry synonyms
huckleberry (related) A small round fruit of a dark blue or red color of several plants in the related. berries (related) blueberry bush. any of numerous shrubs of the genus Vaccinium bearing blueberries.</description></item><item><title>Is Casa Grande AZ a good area?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-casa-grande-az-a-good-area/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-casa-grande-az-a-good-area/</guid><description>Is Casa Grande AZ a good area? Casa Grande is in the 21st percentile for safety, meaning 79% of cities are safer and 21% of cities are more dangerous. The rate of crime in Casa Grande is 43.85 per 1,000 residents during a standard year. People who live in Casa Grande generally consider the north part of the city to be the safest.
How far is Casa Grande AZ from the Mexican border?</description></item><item><title>Is it considered bad luck in China if fish or chicken is served without its head or tail?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-it-considered-bad-luck-in-china-if-fish-or-chicken-is-served-without-its-head-or-tail/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-it-considered-bad-luck-in-china-if-fish-or-chicken-is-served-without-its-head-or-tail/</guid><description>Is it considered bad luck in China if fish or chicken is served without its head or tail? It’s important that the fish is served whole with the head and tail intact, to ensure a good start and finish and to avoid bad luck throughout the year. It’s also important to leave leftovers for the next day because this signifies that the prosperity will overflow.
Is a fish head good luck?</description></item><item><title>Is the University of Alaska Museum of the north in Fairbanks?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-the-university-of-alaska-museum-of-the-north-in-fairbanks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-the-university-of-alaska-museum-of-the-north-in-fairbanks/</guid><description>Is the University of Alaska Museum of the north in Fairbanks? A trip to Fairbanks isn’t complete without a visit to the University of Alaska Museum of the North. Discover fascinating stories about Alaska’s people, places, and wildlife in the museum’s award-winning exhibit galleries – your best introduction to this vast and diverse state.
Where is the UA Museum of the north? Handicap-accessible facility. By Car: Located on the West Ridge of the University of Alaska Fairbanks campus.</description></item><item><title>Is there a common law marriage in Louisiana?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-a-common-law-marriage-in-louisiana/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-a-common-law-marriage-in-louisiana/</guid><description>Is there a common law marriage in Louisiana? Common-law Marriage Is common-law marriage recognized? Louisiana does not and has never legally recognized common-law marriage.
How long does it take to get marriage license in Orleans Parish? The 72-hour waiting period can be waived by a judge or justice of the peace. In Orleans Parish, anyone authorized to solemnize marriages can waive it for nonresidents of Louisiana who opt to marry in Orleans Parish.</description></item><item><title>Is there a lot of poverty in Tanzania?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-a-lot-of-poverty-in-tanzania/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-a-lot-of-poverty-in-tanzania/</guid><description>Is there a lot of poverty in Tanzania? The 2019 Tanzania Mainland Poverty Assessment notes that poverty decreased by eight percentage points in 10 years, down from 34.4% in 2007 to 26.4% in 2018.
What is the average income per person in Tanzania? Economy of Tanzania
StatisticsGDP growth5.4% (2018) 5.8% (2019e) 2.5% (2020f) 5.5% (2021f)GDP per capita$1,105 (nominal, 2019 est.) $3,402 (PPP, 2019 est.)GDP per capita rank158th (nominal, 2019) 154th (PPP, 2019)GDP by sectoragriculture: 23.</description></item><item><title>Is there a train from Vancouver to California?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-a-train-from-vancouver-to-california/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-a-train-from-vancouver-to-california/</guid><description>Is there a train from Vancouver to California? Amtrak is the one and only train line which connects Vancouver, British Columbia to Los Angeles, California. The schedule is relatively limited as the train only runs twice a day.
How long is a train ride from California to Canada? Trip Summary Traveling by train from Los Angeles to Vancouver usually takes around 37 hours and 34 minutes, but the fastest Amtrak train can make the trip in 35 hours and 25 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Is there an ocean that borders Arizona?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-an-ocean-that-borders-arizona/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-there-an-ocean-that-borders-arizona/</guid><description>Is there an ocean that borders Arizona? Arizona. Arizona is a state found in the southwestern region of the country. Southern Arizona is popular for its climate that features mild winters and hot summers. It has California blocking it from the Pacific Ocean as well as Sonora from the Gulf of California.
Which state does not border the Atlantic Ocean? Connecticut, located on the Long Island Sound, also has no actual coastline facing the Atlantic Ocean.</description></item><item><title>Is whaling allowed in Antarctica?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-whaling-allowed-in-antarctica/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/is-whaling-allowed-in-antarctica/</guid><description>Is whaling allowed in Antarctica? That is, because Japan is legally prohibited from killing whales for commercial purposes, Japan is using scientific whaling as a guise under which it can kill Southern Ocean whales, then sell the meat and support the national whaling industry.
Why is whaling a problem in Antarctica? This is a problem because marine mammals like whales, seals, and the birds living in Antarctica all eat krill. A whale can eat huge amounts at a time.</description></item><item><title>What agriculture is in Alaska?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-agriculture-is-in-alaska/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-agriculture-is-in-alaska/</guid><description>What agriculture is in Alaska? The top five Alaskan commodities in terms of cash receipts are aquaculture, greenhouse and nursery production, vegetable production, hay production and cattle and calves production.
What is Alaska known for producing? Alaska’s main export product after oil and natural gas is seafood, primarily salmon, cod, Pollock and crab. Agricultural production is primarily for consumption within the state and includes nursery stock, dairy products, vegetables, and livestock.</description></item><item><title>What are the top 3 industries in Argentina?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-are-the-top-3-industries-in-argentina/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-are-the-top-3-industries-in-argentina/</guid><description>What are the top 3 industries in Argentina? Among the main industries in Argentina are food processing, automobile production, textiles, energy production, and mining. The nation also has a growing chemical industry. The service sector is now the leading component of the Argentine economy.
What type of industries can be found in Argentina? The major industries in Buenos Aires are food processing, motor vehicles, consumer durables, textiles, chemicals and petrochemicals, printing, metallurgy, and steel.</description></item><item><title>What are the top 3 religions in Algeria?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-are-the-top-3-religions-in-algeria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-are-the-top-3-religions-in-algeria/</guid><description>What are the top 3 religions in Algeria? Religion in Algeria
Islam (99.1%)
Christianity (0.4%)
Unaffiliated (0.4%) What are the main religions in Algeria? Islam
Islam is the official religion in Algeria (99.7% of the Algerian population). Majority of the native practice it. Sunni Islam or Muslim religion permeates Algeria in every aspect of life.
What are the top 3 languages spoken in Algeria? Algerian Arabic and Berber are the native languages of over 99% of Algerians, with Algerian Arabic spoken by about 47% and Berber by 53%.</description></item><item><title>What are three major wind systems Weegy?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-are-three-major-wind-systems-weegy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-are-three-major-wind-systems-weegy/</guid><description>What are three major wind systems Weegy? What are the three major wind systems? The 3 Major Global Wind Systems are trade winds, westerlies, and polar easterlies.
What are the 3 main types of global wind patterns? They are the Polar Easterlies, the Prevailing Westerlies, and the Trade Winds. Each one of them rules roughly 30 degrees of latitude, like wind belts around the Earth.
What are the major wind systems found on the earth?</description></item><item><title>What area in Arizona has the best schools?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-area-in-arizona-has-the-best-schools/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-area-in-arizona-has-the-best-schools/</guid><description>What area in Arizona has the best schools? Top School Districts in Arizona, 2020
RankSchool DistrictCity1Catalina Foothills Unified District (4410)Tucson2Queen Creek Unified District (4245)Queen Creek3Sierra Vista Unified District (4175)Sierra Vista4Lake Havasu Unified District (4368)Lake Havasu City Does Flagstaff have good schools? Flagstaff High School 2021 Rankings Flagstaff High School is ranked #7,920 in the National Rankings. Schools are ranked on their performance on state-required tests, graduation and how well they prepare students for college.</description></item><item><title>What can you do in the interior lowlands?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-can-you-do-in-the-interior-lowlands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-can-you-do-in-the-interior-lowlands/</guid><description>What can you do in the interior lowlands? There are a wide variety of things to do in the Interior plains depending on the season, such as cross country, swimming, hiking, fishing, jogging, hunting, and soccer in the summer, and skiing, skating, or hockey in the winter.
What does the interior lowlands include? The Interior Lowlands are located west of the Appalachian Mountains and east of the Great Plains. The main geographic characteristics of this region include: rolling flat lands with many rivers, broad river valleys, and grassy hills.</description></item><item><title>What city is known as the city of peace?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-city-is-known-as-the-city-of-peace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-city-is-known-as-the-city-of-peace/</guid><description>What city is known as the city of peace? While today Baghdad is predominantly associated with war, tragedy, and grief, the Baghdad of the eighth and ninth centuries, also known as Madinat-al-Salam, or the City of Peace, was one of the most advanced cities in the world.
Which city is known as peace city in Japan? Hiroshima was proclaimed a City of Peace by the Japanese parliament in 1949, at the initiative of its mayor, Shinzo Hamai (1905–1968).</description></item><item><title>What climate does the U.S have that Canada doesnt?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-climate-does-the-u.s-have-that-canada-doesnt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-climate-does-the-u.s-have-that-canada-doesnt/</guid><description>What climate does the U.S have that Canada doesnt? “What climate regions are found in the United States but not in Canada? Mediterranean, humid subtropical, desert, and tropical wet.
What types of climates do not exist in the U.S and Canada? Tropical climate does not exist in Canada, the two U.S states that have tropical climates are Florida and Hawaii. What are the Everglades?
What climate regions are located in U.</description></item><item><title>What continent is Czech?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-continent-is-czech/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-continent-is-czech/</guid><description>What continent is Czech? Europe
Czechia/Continent
Is the Czech Republic part of Asia? The Czech Republic is a landlocked country in Central Europe. Czech Republic, popularly referred to as Czechia, is a landlocked country in Europe. Geographically, it is part of Central Europe.
Is Czech Republic a nation state? The Czech Republic also known as Czechia is a landlocked nation state in Central Europe bordered by Germany to the west, Austria to the south, Slovakia to the east and Poland to the northeast.</description></item><item><title>What country in Africa has the most rain?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-country-in-africa-has-the-most-rain/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-country-in-africa-has-the-most-rain/</guid><description>What country in Africa has the most rain? 1.Uganda1,295mm2.Nigeria1,197mm3.Ghana1,169mm4.Rwanda1,164mm5.Ethiopia1,158mm Which country has most rain fall? Colombia
List
RankCountryAverage precipitation (mm in depth per year)1Colombia3,2402São Tomé and Príncipe3,2003Papua New Guinea3,1424Solomon Islands3,028 Why does it never rain in Africa? The cooler temperatures in the north weakened the high altitude Tropical Easterly Jet, which consistently brought moisture into northern Africa. Due to the weakening of the Tropical Easterly Jet, the African Easterly Jet strengthened, which indirectly inhibits rainfall in northern Africa.</description></item><item><title>What did Dirk Hartog find in Australia?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-did-dirk-hartog-find-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-did-dirk-hartog-find-in-australia/</guid><description>What did Dirk Hartog find in Australia? Evidence of first European sightings In 1616, Dutch skipper, Dirk Hartog, along with upper-merchant Gillis Miebais, in the ship Eendracht, accidentally discovered what proved to be the west coast of the Unknown South Land while sailing northwards.
Who came to Australia in 1616? Dirk Hartog
On 25 October 1616, at approximately 26° latitude south, Hartog and crew came unexpectedly upon “various islands, which were, however, found uninhabited.</description></item><item><title>What does a black cloud with rain mean?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-does-a-black-cloud-with-rain-mean/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-does-a-black-cloud-with-rain-mean/</guid><description>What does a black cloud with rain mean? Black clouds usually indicate that rain is imminent because the cloud is saturated with moisture.
What kind of clouds produce rain? The prefix “nimbo-” or the suffix “-nimbus” are low-level clouds that have their bases below 2,000 meters (6,500 feet) above the Earth. Clouds that produce rain and snow fall into this category. (“Nimbus” comes from the Latin word for “rain.”) Two examples are the nimbostratus or cumulonimbus clouds.</description></item><item><title>What does it mean when shares are beneficially held?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-does-it-mean-when-shares-are-beneficially-held/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-does-it-mean-when-shares-are-beneficially-held/</guid><description>What does it mean when shares are beneficially held? ‘Beneficially held’ means that the owner of the shares gets the direct benefit from the shares. Direct benefits include dividend payments. If the shareholder is holding the shares on behalf of another person, organisation or trust, they are not beneficially held.
What is meant by beneficial ownership? A beneficial owner is an individual who ultimately owns or controls more than 25% of a company’s shares or voting rights, or who otherwise exercise control over the company or its management.</description></item><item><title>What ethnicity are most people in Brazil?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-ethnicity-are-most-people-in-brazil/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-ethnicity-are-most-people-in-brazil/</guid><description>What ethnicity are most people in Brazil? For more additional, identity-specific information about Brazil visit the Diversity &amp;amp; Inclusion Guides to Brazil. 211,715,973 (July 2020 est.) Ethnic groups: White 47.7%, Mulatto (mixed white and black) 43.1%, Black 7.6%, Asian 1.1%, indigenous 0.4% (2010 est.)
How many ethnicities are there in Brazil? Indigenous peoples live in every state of Brazil and represent 305 different ethnic groups and 274 indigenous languages.
What ethnicity are people in Rio?</description></item><item><title>What happens to water molecules when fog?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-happens-to-water-molecules-when-fog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-happens-to-water-molecules-when-fog/</guid><description>What happens to water molecules when fog? Fog shows up when water vapor, or water in its gaseous form, condenses. During condensation, molecules of water vapor combine to make tiny liquid water droplets that hang in the air. You can see fog because of these tiny water droplets.
Do water molecules absorb or release energy? During the processes of condensation, freezing, and deposition, water releases energy. The energy released allows the water molecules to change their bonding pattern and transform to a lower energy state.</description></item><item><title>What is Benicia CA known for?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-benicia-ca-known-for/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-benicia-ca-known-for/</guid><description>What is Benicia CA known for? The City of Benicia is a Bay Area City located adjacent to the Carquinez Strait, which is part of San Francisco Bay. A waterfront City of 28,000, Benicia is known for its small-town charm, history, and high quality of life. Benicia offers an abundance of leisure and recreational activities.
When was Benicia the capital of California? 1853
Benicia State Capitol History: Built in 1852 as Benicia’s city hall, the site became California’s Capitol in 1853.</description></item><item><title>What is Nabisco known for?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-nabisco-known-for/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-nabisco-known-for/</guid><description>What is Nabisco known for? The National Biscuit Company was formed in 1898 when the American Biscuit Company merged with the New York Biscuit Company. Better known as Nabisco, it went on to introduce a number of popular consumer brands such as Oreo cookies (1912) and Ritz crackers (1934).
What did Nabisco make? Its products include Chips Ahoy!, Belvita, Oreo cookies, Ritz Crackers, Teddy Grahams, Triscuit crackers, Fig Newtons, and Wheat Thins for the United States, United Kingdom, Mexico, Bolivia, Venezuela, and other parts of South America.</description></item><item><title>What is on the NCR flag?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-on-the-ncr-flag/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-on-the-ncr-flag/</guid><description>What is on the NCR flag? When asked where the original NCR capital was located, you answer Shady Sands. And when asked what the NCR’s flag is emblazoned with, you answer a double-headed bear.
Who is the most famous person in NCR history? Q1 – Tandi is the most popular NCR president in history. Q2 – Shady Sands was the original name of the NCR Capitol.
Can I kill Orris? Killing Orris after talking to him about not killing the thugs will not affect the outcome of the quest.</description></item><item><title>What is Sydney city called?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-sydney-city-called/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-sydney-city-called/</guid><description>What is Sydney city called? The Emerald City
Why Sydney Is Also Known As ‘The Emerald City’ Sydney — a coastal metropolis whose five million residents make it the largest city in Australia — is famous for many things. The glittering harbour, complemented by landmarks like the Sydney Opera House and the Sydney Harbour Bridge.
How many city are in Australia? 5 cities
Australia has 5 cities with more than a million people, 14 cities with between 100,000 and 1 million people, and 31 cities with between 10,000 and 100,000 people.</description></item><item><title>What is the Aboriginal word for happy place?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-aboriginal-word-for-happy-place/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-aboriginal-word-for-happy-place/</guid><description>What is the Aboriginal word for happy place? Cooinda
Cooinda is an aboriginal word meaning ‘Happy Place’ and that’s what owners Jonathan and Kerrie want their guests to feel during their stay.
What does migaloo mean in Aboriginal? a white person
The word migaloo – “a white person” – comes from Biri and other northern Queensland languages, where it originally meant “a ghost, a spirit”; many Australians are familiar with this word as a name for the albino humpback whale that migrates along the east coast of Australia.</description></item><item><title>What is the Afghan money called?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-afghan-money-called/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-afghan-money-called/</guid><description>What is the Afghan money called? Afghan afghani
Afghanistan/Currencies
Who prints Afghanistan currency? Central Bank of Afghanistan
Da Afghanistan Bank (Central Bank of Afghanistan) is to print and distribute new banknotes to country’s money circulation, bank officials said Tuesday, pointing out that the Afghan parliament has permitted the central bank to print up to 100 billion Afghanis (US$ 20 million).
Is Pakistani currency used in Afghanistan? The Pakistani currency, which otherwise had no purpose in Afghanistan, was also used for funding sub-nationalist groups to undertake sabotage activities and hit national unity inside Pakistan.</description></item><item><title>What is the biggest highway in Australia?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-biggest-highway-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-biggest-highway-in-australia/</guid><description>What is the biggest highway in Australia? Highway 1
Highway 1, Australia – Total length: 9,009 miles (14,500 km) Trans-Siberian Highway – Total length: 6,800 miles (11,000 km)
What is A1 highway? A1 road (Australia) may refer to several roads part of the highway 1 including the following segments: A1 highway (Victoria), connecting New South Wales via Melbourne and Portland to South Australia. A1 (New South Wales), consisting of several discrete sections including the Princes Highway and Pacific Highway.</description></item><item><title>What is the capital city population of Northwest Territories?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-capital-city-population-of-northwest-territories/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-capital-city-population-of-northwest-territories/</guid><description>What is the capital city population of Northwest Territories? With a population just over 20,000 people, Yellowknife is both the capital and only city in the Northwest Territories.
What is capital of Nunavut? Iqaluit
Nunavut/Capitals
Iqaluit, formerly Frobisher Bay, city, capital of Nunavut territory and headquarters of Baffin region, Canada.
Is Yellowknife the only city in NWT? Yellowknife (/ˈjɛloʊnaɪf/; Dogrib: Sǫǫ̀mbak’è) is the capital, only city, and largest community in the Northwest Territories, Canada.</description></item><item><title>What is the coldest temperature ever in Alaska?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-coldest-temperature-ever-in-alaska/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-coldest-temperature-ever-in-alaska/</guid><description>What is the coldest temperature ever in Alaska? Alaska Weather Records
Lowest Temperature. -79.8° F (-62° C) at Prospect Creek on January 23, 1971.
Highest Temperature. 100° F (38° C) at Fort Yukon on June 27, 1915.
Lowest Annual Normal Temperature. 9.3° F (-12.6° C) at Utqiagvik (Barrow)
Lowest Summer Normal Temperature. June–August.
Lowest Winter Normal Temperature. How cold does it get in Alaska Fahrenheit?</description></item><item><title>What is the correct abbreviation for Arkansas?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-correct-abbreviation-for-arkansas/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-correct-abbreviation-for-arkansas/</guid><description>What is the correct abbreviation for Arkansas? AR
StateAbbrev- iationPostal codeAlabamaAla.ALAlaskaAlaskaAKArizonaAriz.AZArkansasArk.AR How do you abbreviate States? The names of eight states are never abbreviated in datelines or text: Alaska, Hawaii, Idaho, Iowa, Maine, Ohio, Texas and Utah. Memory aid: States with five or fewer letters, plus Alaska and Hawaii, are never abbreviated.
What state abbreviation is MI? MICH
Michigan Wolverines football/Abbreviations
Do state abbreviations have periods? Do not use state abbreviations simply to save time or space except in an address on an envelope or list.</description></item><item><title>What is the ethnic makeup of Surrey BC?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-ethnic-makeup-of-surrey-bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-ethnic-makeup-of-surrey-bc/</guid><description>What is the ethnic makeup of Surrey BC? The largest visible minority population are that of the South Asian, making up 57.76 per cent of the total visible minority population. The second largest group are the Chinese, making up 39,890 people. Following Chinese is Filipino that is 10.95 per cent of the visible minority population.
What is the elevation of Langley BC? 15 m
Langley/Elevation
Why is Surrey so dangerous? A lot of the violent crime that occurs in Surrey is gang or drug related.</description></item><item><title>What is the Hisor fortress?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-hisor-fortress/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-hisor-fortress/</guid><description>What is the Hisor fortress? A popular day trip from Dushanbe, the fortress of Hisor stands on a hill commanding the valley between 2 mountain ranges. These days, the site is occupied by a newly-built fortress, meant to evoke an 18th-century fortress destroyed by the Red Army when they conquered Tajikistan.
Who built Bala Hissar Kabul? Babur
Babur developed a palace within the Bala Hissar, about which we have few details, although we know that he himself preferred to camp out in one or other of his gardens.</description></item><item><title>What is the largest airport in the world by size?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-largest-airport-in-the-world-by-size/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-largest-airport-in-the-world-by-size/</guid><description>What is the largest airport in the world by size? King Fahd International Airport
The King Fahd International Airport in Dammam, Saudi Arabia is the world’s largest airport property by area. Taking up nearly 300 square miles, King Fahd International is about the size of New York City.
Which airport has the most land? King Fahd International Airport (Dammam, Saudi Arabia) The world’s largest airport by land area is King Fahd International Airport (KFIA).</description></item><item><title>What is the maximum penalty for poaching?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-maximum-penalty-for-poaching/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-maximum-penalty-for-poaching/</guid><description>What is the maximum penalty for poaching? The maximum sentence for felony poaching is two years in prison and a fine between $5,000 and $10,000. Wanton destruction of a big game animal is also a serious poaching offense. The punishment for poaching under this law is one year in jail and up to $10,000 in fines.
Is poaching a problem in China? Poaching, transporting and trading in wildlife is illegal on the mainland and those who sell rare and endangered species could face criminal charges.</description></item><item><title>What is the temperature at the top of Mount Whitney?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-temperature-at-the-top-of-mount-whitney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-is-the-temperature-at-the-top-of-mount-whitney/</guid><description>What is the temperature at the top of Mount Whitney? Mount Whitney Weather (Days 0-3): Mostly dry. Mild temperatures (max 45°F on Thu afternoon, min 39°F on Tue night). Wind will be generally light.°CTue 10Max4341Min4339Chill °F3737 Does Mount Whitney have snow? January to April – If you are equipped for winter mountaineering, this would be quite the adventure! But for most of us, Whitney is a summer hike. May and June – There is always snow on Mt.</description></item><item><title>What lake in Africa is drying up?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-lake-in-africa-is-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-lake-in-africa-is-drying-up/</guid><description>What lake in Africa is drying up? Lake Chad
Lake Chad has literally gone from being an oasis in the desert, to being just desert. Spanning the countries of Chad, Nigeria, Niger and Cameroon and bordering the Sahara desert, Lake Chad has contracted by a massive 95% between 1963 and 2001.
Does East Africa have water? Eastern Africa is home to some of the greatest water sources in the world. The three most notable water bodies and systems and of relevance to the East Africa region include: Lake Victoria – Africa’s largest lake and the world’s second-largest freshwater lake, and.</description></item><item><title>What main holidays are celebrated in China?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-main-holidays-are-celebrated-in-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-main-holidays-are-celebrated-in-china/</guid><description>What main holidays are celebrated in China? The coming Qixi Festival, China Valentine’s Day, falls on August 14, 2021. China has seven legal holidays in a year, including New Year’s Day, Chinese New Year (Spring Festival), Qingming Festival, May Day, Dragon Boat Festival, Mid-Autumn Day and National Day.
What are the special days in China? List of Holidays in China in 2021
DayDateHoliday NameMondaySep 20Mid Autumn Festival HolidayTuesdaySep 21Mid Autumn FestivalFridayOct 01Chinese National DaySaturdayOct 02Chinese National Day Holiday What are the 4 Chinese holidays?</description></item><item><title>What natural disaster does Canada have?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-natural-disaster-does-canada-have/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-natural-disaster-does-canada-have/</guid><description>What natural disaster does Canada have? When nature’s in a bad mood, here’s what can happen.
Forest fires. Forty-five percent of forest fires in Canada are set off by lightning, but Mother Nature is not solely responsible for these disasters!
Floods and torrential rains.
Hurricanes.
Tornadoes.
Volcanic eruptions.
Earthquakes.
Avalanches and landslides.
Ice storms. What are the 8 natural hazards?</description></item><item><title>What plants are on Madagascar?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-plants-are-on-madagascar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-plants-are-on-madagascar/</guid><description>What plants are on Madagascar? Madagascar’s Endemic Plants and Flowers
Za Baobab (Andasonia Za Baill.) Bismarck palm (Bismarckia nobilis) Tapia (Uapaca bojeri Baill.) Madagascar banana tree (Ensete perrieri Cheesman) Tahina palm (Tahina spectabilis) Octopus trees (Didierea madagascariensis Baill.) The Madagascar periwinkle (Catharanthus roseus) What animals are unique to Madagascar? 10 fascinating creatures only found in Madagascar
The Madagascar Pochard. Now, to start, we have a Pochard duck. Giraffe Weevil.</description></item><item><title>What religion is practiced most in South Asia?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-religion-is-practiced-most-in-south-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-religion-is-practiced-most-in-south-asia/</guid><description>What religion is practiced most in South Asia? Asia is noted for its diversity of culture. Islam and Hinduism are the largest religions in Asia with approximately 1.2 billion adherents each….Eastern Asia.
CountrySouth KoreaBuddhist%22.90Folk religionPop.385,440%0.80Other religionPop.96,360 What are the major world religions that have emerged in South Asia? South Asia is the birthplace of four of the world’s religions: Hinduism, Buddhism, Sikhism, and Jainism. Three that come from West Asia: Christianity, Islam, and Judaism arrived later.</description></item><item><title>What resulted from the Greek rebellion in Asia Minor?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-resulted-from-the-greek-rebellion-in-asia-minor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-resulted-from-the-greek-rebellion-in-asia-minor/</guid><description>What resulted from the Greek rebellion in Asia Minor? Although Asia Minor had been brought back into the Persian fold, Darius vowed to punish Athens and Eretria for their support of the revolt….Ionian Revolt.
Date499–493 BCResultDecisive Persian victoryTerritorial changesPersia re-establishes control over Greek regions in Asia Minor and Cyprus. When did the Greek colonies in Asia Minor revolt? Ionian revolt, uprising (499–494 bce) of some of the Ionian cities of Asia Minor against their Persian overlords.</description></item><item><title>What time of year are tides the highest?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-time-of-year-are-tides-the-highest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-time-of-year-are-tides-the-highest/</guid><description>What time of year are tides the highest? spring tides
In the lunar month, the highest tides occur roughly every 14 days, at the new and full moons, when the gravitational pull of the Moon and the Sun are in alignment. These highest tides in the lunar cycle are called spring tides.
Where does the greatest tidal range occur quizlet? The Bay of Fundy has the greatest tidal ranges on Earth.</description></item><item><title>What transport is used in Antarctica?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-transport-is-used-in-antarctica/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-transport-is-used-in-antarctica/</guid><description>What transport is used in Antarctica? Transport in Antarctica takes place by air, using fixed-wing aircraft and helicopters. Runways and helicopter pads have to be kept snow free to ensure safe take off and landing conditions. Antarctica has 20 airports, but there are no developed public-access airports or landing facilities.
How was Antarctica in the past? It may be hard to believe, but Antarctica was once covered in towering forests. One hundred million years ago, the Earth was in the grip of an extreme Greenhouse Effect.</description></item><item><title>What type of air mass would be responsible for heavy summer rain showers?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-type-of-air-mass-would-be-responsible-for-heavy-summer-rain-showers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-type-of-air-mass-would-be-responsible-for-heavy-summer-rain-showers/</guid><description>What type of air mass would be responsible for heavy summer rain showers? Maritime polar air mass causes heavy snow showers and low temperatures at Buffalo, New York. Maritime tropical air mass causes hot and muggy summer weather in the Midwest and the East. Maritime tropical air mass causes afternoon thunderstorms everyday along the Gulf Coast.
What type of air mass would be responsible for hot dry summer weather in southern Arizona?</description></item><item><title>What was everyday life in medieval Europe?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-was-everyday-life-in-medieval-europe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-was-everyday-life-in-medieval-europe/</guid><description>What was everyday life in medieval Europe? The majority of people living during the Middle Ages lived in the country and worked as farmers. Usually there was a local lord who lived in a large house called a manor or a castle. Local peasants would work the land for the lord. The peasants were called the lord’s “villeins”, which was like a servant.
What was the daily life of a peasant in the Middle Ages?</description></item><item><title>What was the minimum hourly wage in 1965?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-was-the-minimum-hourly-wage-in-1965/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-was-the-minimum-hourly-wage-in-1965/</guid><description>What was the minimum hourly wage in 1965? $1.25
Minimum hourly wage of workers in jobs first covered by
Effective Date1938 Act 11961 Amendments 2Sep 3, 1963$1.25Sep 3, 1964$1.15Sep 3, 1965$1.25Feb 1, 1967$1.40$1.40 What was California’s minimum wage in 1963? The 1961 amendments greatly expanded the FLSA’s scope in the retail trade sector and increased the minimum for previously covered workers to $1.15 an hour effective September 1961 and to $1.</description></item><item><title>What was the purpose of the Haymarket Riot?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-was-the-purpose-of-the-haymarket-riot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/what-was-the-purpose-of-the-haymarket-riot/</guid><description>What was the purpose of the Haymarket Riot? The May 4, 1886, rally at Haymarket Square was organized by labor radicals to protest the killing and wounding of several workers by the Chicago police during a strike the day before at the McCormick Reaper Works.
What was the result of the Haymarket Square riot of 1886? The Haymarket Riot took place in Chicago on May 4, 1886. Seven policemen and several protesters were killed, and the event led to the execution of four radicals.</description></item><item><title>Where did Tommy Shaw grow up?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/where-did-tommy-shaw-grow-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/where-did-tommy-shaw-grow-up/</guid><description>Where did Tommy Shaw grow up? Montgomery
Tommy Shaw, 2010 Shaw was born on September 11, 1953, in Montgomery to Dalton Earl Shaw and Mildred Uline Shaw; he is the youngest of four children. His father was a pipefitter and his mother a nurse. When he was two years old his family moved to Prattville, Autauga County, where he lived up until the age of 12.
Where is Tommy Shaw from?</description></item><item><title>Where do most Somali immigrants live?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/where-do-most-somali-immigrants-live/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/where-do-most-somali-immigrants-live/</guid><description>Where do most Somali immigrants live? About two thirds of all Somalis who live outside Somalia live in neighbouring countries Kenya, Ethiopia, Djibouti and Yemen. Kenya hosted more than 313,000 in April 2017.
Why did Somalis move to Canada? The overwhelming majority of Somalis entered Canada as refugees under the Refugee Class of the Immigration Act. As they began the process of resettling in Canada, Somali refugees encountered enormous difficulties in adjusting to Canada’s socio-economic and political environment.</description></item><item><title>Where the US Bicycle Hall of Fame is located in?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/where-the-us-bicycle-hall-of-fame-is-located-in/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/where-the-us-bicycle-hall-of-fame-is-located-in/</guid><description>Where the US Bicycle Hall of Fame is located in? Central Park
The Hall of Fame is located in Central Park, downtown Davis, CA, which provides ample room to relax after a long ride.
What is the largest event in the cycling world? The Cape Town Cycle Tour
The Cape Town Cycle Tour is the largest timed cycling event in the world. Attracting in excess of 35,000 cyclists from around the globe each year, this iconic event is definitely a unique experience for participants and spectators alike.</description></item><item><title>Which city is bigger Orlando or Jacksonville?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-city-is-bigger-orlando-or-jacksonville/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-city-is-bigger-orlando-or-jacksonville/</guid><description>Which city is bigger Orlando or Jacksonville? Jacksonville (or Jax, as it’s sometimes known) is by far the larger city of the two (892,000 people against Orlando’s 280,000) but primarily because the city’s square mileage is larger. In fact, at 875 sq. miles, Jacksonville is the largest city by area in the lower 48.
Is Jacksonville the biggest city in the world? Jacksonville is the most populous city in Florida, and is the largest city by area in the contiguous United States as of 2020.</description></item><item><title>Which country is the largest producer of maple syrup?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-country-is-the-largest-producer-of-maple-syrup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-country-is-the-largest-producer-of-maple-syrup/</guid><description>Which country is the largest producer of maple syrup? Canada
The vast majority of this comes from the province of Quebec, which is the world’s largest producer, with about 70 percent of global production. Canada exported more than C$362 million of maple syrup in 2016.
What country produces maple syrup? Canada is the world’s leading producer and exporter of maple products, accounting for 71 per cent of the global market. In 2016, Canadian producers exported 45 million kg of maple products, with a value of $381 million.</description></item><item><title>Which country uses 251 code?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-country-uses-251-code/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-country-uses-251-code/</guid><description>Which country uses 251 code? National Numbering Plan (NNP) of Ethiopia
Country code:+251International prefix:00National prefix:0Length of area code:two (2) digitsLength of subscriber number:seven (7) digits What does Ethiopia number start with? 251
The international country code for Ethiopia is 251 and you need to drop the first zero from the number when calling from abroad. To call an international number from within Ethiopia, dial 00 followed by the number. Mobile numbers begin with ’09’.</description></item><item><title>Which is the fattest state in Australia?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-is-the-fattest-state-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-is-the-fattest-state-in-australia/</guid><description>Which is the fattest state in Australia? Tasmania
Australia’s Health Report conducted more than 755,000 health checks in Priceline pharmacy stores over a two-year period. Tasmania has been named the unhealthiest state in the country with the highest stress levels, body mass index (BMI), blood pressure and smoking rates.
Where is Australia in the fattest country list? Australia revealed as the fifth fattest country in the WORLD with three in every five people overweight and 30 per cent of people classed as obese.</description></item><item><title>Which major landforms and or waterways do the US and Canada share?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-major-landforms-and-or-waterways-do-the-us-and-canada-share/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-major-landforms-and-or-waterways-do-the-us-and-canada-share/</guid><description>Which major landforms and or waterways do the US and Canada share? Which major landforms and/or waterways do the United States and Canada share? Rocky Mountains, St. Lawrence, Great Lakes.
What are the landforms in United States? Important Landforms in the U.S.
Appalachian Mountains. The Appalachian Mountains may be some of the oldest mountains on earth. Rocky Mountains. Great Salt Lake. Grand Canyon. Great Plains. Mississippi River. Mojave Desert &amp;amp; Death Valley.</description></item><item><title>Which mountain range divides the Antarctica into two parts?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-mountain-range-divides-the-antarctica-into-two-parts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-mountain-range-divides-the-antarctica-into-two-parts/</guid><description>Which mountain range divides the Antarctica into two parts? Trans-Antarctic Mountains
The Trans-Antarctic Mountains divide Antarctica into two parts, East Antarctica and West Antarctica.
What mountains are in eastern Antarctica? List of mountains of East Antarctica
Rank of mountainsNameParent Range1Dome AEast Antarctic Ice Sheet2Nilsen PlateauEast Antarctic Ice Sheet3Dome FEast Antarctic Ice Sheet4Mount MenziesEast Antarctic Ice Sheet Which is the third major mountain range in Antarctica? The third major range is called the Transantarctic Mountains, which runs north to south and splits the continent into East and West Antarctica.</description></item><item><title>Which products are made in Australia?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-products-are-made-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-products-are-made-in-australia/</guid><description>Which products are made in Australia? It was a reminder that many Australian pantry staples are foreign-owned despite their Aussie roots.
Arnott’s. Key products: TimTam, Shapes, Jatz. Bushells. Key products: Tea and coffee. Uncle Tobys. Key products: Roll Ups, Cheerios, Le Snak, Oats. Rosella. Key products: Tomato sauce, soup, chutney. Is anything manufactured in Australia? Although the primary manufacturing industry is one of the major industries in Australia, manufacturing in Australia is still a significant industry.</description></item><item><title>Which territory is the least densely populated?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-territory-is-the-least-densely-populated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/which-territory-is-the-least-densely-populated/</guid><description>Which territory is the least densely populated? Greenland
Greenland is the least densely populated territory in the world with 0.14 people per sq. km.
Is Sydney or Melbourne more densely populated? According to Demographia’s list, out of the 1,040 cities surveyed, Melbourne’s population density of an estimated 1,500 people/ km2 is ranked 955th. The same Demographia-sponsored survey listed Sydney as 43rd in terms of urban footprint size (2,037 km2).
Where is Australia’s greatest population density?</description></item><item><title>Who is the first African president?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-is-the-first-african-president/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-is-the-first-african-president/</guid><description>Who is the first African president? The African National Congress won a 63% share of the vote at the election, and Mandela, as leader of the ANC, was inaugurated on 10 May 1994 as the country’s first Black President, with the National Party’s F.W. de Klerk as his first deputy and Thabo Mbeki as the second in the Government of National Unity.
How many leaders has the Central African Republic had?</description></item><item><title>Who owns the land the White House is on?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-owns-the-land-the-white-house-is-on/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-owns-the-land-the-white-house-is-on/</guid><description>Who owns the land the White House is on? the National Park Service
The White House is owned by the National Park Service and is part of the President’s Park. When a president enters office, he and his family are given $100,000 for redecorating, but some, including President Obama, opt to pay for the redecoration on their own.
What buildings are on the White House grounds? The Grounds
The White House Building.</description></item><item><title>Who runs Chennai airport?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-runs-chennai-airport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-runs-chennai-airport/</guid><description>Who runs Chennai airport? Chennai airport is the centre of the southern flight information region (FIR), one of the four FIRs that the Indian air space is divided into. The regional executive director (RED) is responsible for the air traffic services over the Chennai FIR and airport management on ground at the airports in South India.
How many terminals are there in Chennai airport? three terminals
– Chennai International Airport has three terminals.</description></item><item><title>Who was mayor in Birmingham in 1963?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-was-mayor-in-birmingham-in-1963/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/who-was-mayor-in-birmingham-in-1963/</guid><description>Who was mayor in Birmingham in 1963? Albert Boutwell
Albert BoutwellPreceded byWilliam G. HardwickSucceeded byJames B. Allen22nd Mayor of Birmingham, AlabamaIn office 1963–1967 What happened in Birmingham Alabama in April 1963? In April 1963 King and the Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC) joined with Birmingham, Alabama’s existing local movement, the Alabama Christian Movement for Human Rights (ACMHR), in a massive direct action campaign to attack the city’s segregation system by putting pressure on Birmingham’s merchants during …</description></item><item><title>Why is it called Peking Man?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/why-is-it-called-peking-man/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/why-is-it-called-peking-man/</guid><description>Why is it called Peking Man? Peking man, extinct hominin of the species Homo erectus, known from fossils found at Zhoukoudian near Beijing. Peking man was identified as a member of the human lineage by Davidson Black in 1927 on the basis of a single tooth. The limb bones are indistinguishable from those of modern humans. …
How many years ago did Peking Man live? During excavations near Peking (Beijing), China, between 1929 and 1937, researchers discovered several partial skulls of the species Homo erectus.</description></item><item><title>Why is the Murray river important to people?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/why-is-the-murray-river-important-to-people/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/why-is-the-murray-river-important-to-people/</guid><description>Why is the Murray river important to people? More than 3 million Australians rely on the Murray-Darling Basin rivers for drinking water, including Canberra and Adelaide. Home to more than 40 Aboriginal Nations with deep cultural, social, environmental, spiritual and economic connection to their lands and waters.
What are the main uses of the Murray river to the people? A total of 3.6 million people (including the entire population of Adelaide which is not in the Basin) rely on water from the Basin rivers for many uses, including drinking, washing, farming and irrigation.</description></item><item><title>Why is the water cycle never ending?</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/why-is-the-water-cycle-never-ending/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/why-is-the-water-cycle-never-ending/</guid><description>Why is the water cycle never ending? Water moves from the earth to the air to the earth again meaning we are using the same water that was once used by the dinosaurs. Water moves from clouds to land and back to the oceans in a never ending cycle.
Does the water cycle ever end explain? There is no start or end to the water cycle, but for explanation purposes we will start at the sun.</description></item></channel></rss>