<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>webdev on Dev Arc</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/tags/webdev/</link><description>Recent content in webdev on Dev Arc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 06:03:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/tags/webdev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 amazing web apps for developers</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/2-amazing-web-apps-for-developers-33i2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 06:03:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/2-amazing-web-apps-for-developers-33i2/</guid><description>Amazing tools for developers to that might come in handy and increase productivity when working with images.
removebg If you want to remove the background of any photo just select your image and download the image with the background removed. It&amp;rsquo;s fast and really great.
Profile Pic Maker You can use it to generate professional profile pics from any photo. It uses background removal AI, beautifies your photo, and you can also choose from different backgrounds for your image.</description></item><item><title>001 The Week In Stories Tech Salaries Freebies and Dev Things</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/001-the-week-in-stories-tech-salaries-freebies-and-dev-things-2bmi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 03:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/001-the-week-in-stories-tech-salaries-freebies-and-dev-things-2bmi/</guid><description>Hi all!
Welcome to the first edition of {Tech &amp;amp; Dev}.
At the beginning of this year, I made a goal for myself to be more consistent with creating things — whether it be through my writing or making mini-apps on the side to learn new things and keep up with the tech.
The point is that I make and keep making — come rain, shine, lockdowns, homeschooling, and whatever life will throw at me in 2022.</description></item><item><title>3 Simple steps to increase speed efficiency while working browsing</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-simple-steps-to-increase-speed-efficiency-while-working-browsing-42n0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-simple-steps-to-increase-speed-efficiency-while-working-browsing-42n0/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re like me then you prefer to do everything on the computer without touching the mouse. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like a game sometimes. How can I open this program or browse this webpage without needing to lift my hands off of the keyboard? More specifically, how can I keep my fingers on the wasdf-jkli keys while navigating? Afterall, lifting my hand up to reach for the arrow keys is almost the same distance away as my mouse is.</description></item><item><title>1 line of code How to reverse all words of a string</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-all-words-of-a-string-n26/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 15:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-all-words-of-a-string-n26/</guid><description>1 const reverseWords = (str) =&amp;gt; str.split(&amp;#34; &amp;#34;).map((word) =&amp;gt; [...word].reverse().join(&amp;#34;&amp;#34;)).join(&amp;#34;&amp;#34;); Returns the string with all words reversed
Improved version with unicode support 1 const reverseWords = (str) =&amp;gt; str.replace(/(\p{L}+)/gu, (word) =&amp;gt; [...word].reverse().join(&amp;#39;&amp;#39;)); The repository and npm package You can find the all the utility functions from this series at github.com/martinkr/onelinecode The library is also published to npm as @onelinecode for your convenience.</description></item><item><title>1 line of code How to reverse a string</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-a-string-2pga/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 14:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-a-string-2pga/</guid><description>1 const reverseString = str =&amp;gt; [...str].reverse().join(&amp;#34;&amp;#34;); Returns the reversed string.
The repository &amp;amp;amp; npm package You can find the all the utility functions from this series at github.com/martinkr/onelinecode The library is also published to npm as @onelinecode for your convenience.
The code and the npm package will be updated every time I publish a new article.
Follow me on Twitter: @martinkr and consider to buy me a coffee</description></item></channel></rss>