<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Dev Arc</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Dev Arc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 06:03:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 amazing web apps for developers</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/2-amazing-web-apps-for-developers-33i2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 06:03:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/2-amazing-web-apps-for-developers-33i2/</guid><description>Amazing tools for developers to that might come in handy and increase productivity when working with images.
removebg If you want to remove the background of any photo just select your image and download the image with the background removed. It&amp;rsquo;s fast and really great.
Profile Pic Maker You can use it to generate professional profile pics from any photo. It uses background removal AI, beautifies your photo, and you can also choose from different backgrounds for your image.</description></item><item><title>001 The Week In Stories Tech Salaries Freebies and Dev Things</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/001-the-week-in-stories-tech-salaries-freebies-and-dev-things-2bmi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 03:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/001-the-week-in-stories-tech-salaries-freebies-and-dev-things-2bmi/</guid><description>Hi all!
Welcome to the first edition of {Tech &amp;amp; Dev}.
At the beginning of this year, I made a goal for myself to be more consistent with creating things — whether it be through my writing or making mini-apps on the side to learn new things and keep up with the tech.
The point is that I make and keep making — come rain, shine, lockdowns, homeschooling, and whatever life will throw at me in 2022.</description></item><item><title>03 Understanding Blockchain with ethersjs 4 Tasks of interacting with smart contract</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/03-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-interacting-with-smart-contract-3ef6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:28:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/03-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-interacting-with-smart-contract-3ef6/</guid><description>In third part of this ethers.js tutorial, we will use ethers.js to interact with smart contract.
What we do here is a little beyond the scope of learning ethers.js:
Write a ERC20 token smart contract with OpenZeppelin Deploy the smart contract to Hardhat local testnet Interact with smart contract using Ethers.js Task 1: Write ERC20 token smart contract We will write an ERC20 token smart contract using the verified and popular solidity token library OpenZeppelin.</description></item><item><title>02 Understanding Blockchain with ethersjs 4 Tasks of wallet</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/02-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-wallet-nn5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/02-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-wallet-nn5/</guid><description>Ethers.js provides functions to deal with Ethereum blockchain wallet. You can find Ethers.js documents about Wallet here.
Get a better understanding with the following tasks:
Task 1: Create wallet from mnemonic and privateKey Task 1.1 Create wallet from mnemonic 1 2 3 4 5 6 mnemonic=&amp;#39;myth like bonus scare over problem client lizard pioneer submit female collect&amp;#39; //check whether it is valid mnemonic ethers.</description></item><item><title>01 Understanding Blockchain with ethersjs 4 Tasks of Basics and Transfer</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/01-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-basics-and-transfer-5d17/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:23:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/01-understanding-blockchain-with-ethersjs-4-tasks-of-basics-and-transfer-5d17/</guid><description>As a web3 developer, you can play with Ethereum blockchain using Ethers.js to get a deeper understanding. This 3-parts tutorial lists 12 tasks for you.
Ethers.js is a Javascript API for Ethereum blockchain which can work with Mainnet, testnet such as Ropsten, Rinkeby, local testnet, Layer 2 and sidechains.
We will use Hardhat Ethereum development environment to set up a playground as it can provide all the components we need:</description></item><item><title>2 Day of 100 Days of Code</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/2-day-100-days-of-code-446c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/2-day-100-days-of-code-446c/</guid><description>Day 2 of #100DaysOfCode started with&amp;amp;hellip; refresh my PHP knowledge. I made the documentation / wiki of the DiscordCustomRPC.py repository a little more understandable. I also updated the Python rewrite of the AntiScamBot backend, but it&amp;rsquo;s not yet merged.</description></item><item><title>3 Simple steps to increase speed efficiency while working browsing</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-simple-steps-to-increase-speed-efficiency-while-working-browsing-42n0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-simple-steps-to-increase-speed-efficiency-while-working-browsing-42n0/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re like me then you prefer to do everything on the computer without touching the mouse. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like a game sometimes. How can I open this program or browse this webpage without needing to lift my hands off of the keyboard? More specifically, how can I keep my fingers on the wasdf-jkli keys while navigating? Afterall, lifting my hand up to reach for the arrow keys is almost the same distance away as my mouse is.</description></item><item><title>3 Ways To Learn Coding Within Three Months</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-ways-to-learn-coding-within-three-months-enb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:22:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-ways-to-learn-coding-within-three-months-enb/</guid><description>If you desire to code but have no plan on how to get started then this article is for you. Desiring to code is one thing and being consistent about it is another thing. Most beginners give up when things start to go south. Welcome to anythingprogramming.com, in this article I will list some guides that will help you to stay on track without burning out.
Why Do You Desire To Code?</description></item><item><title>3 piece of advice for junior developers</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-piece-of-advice-for-junior-developers-6gg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 14:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/3-piece-of-advice-for-junior-developers-6gg/</guid><description>A few months ago, my manager asked me if I&amp;rsquo;d like to facilitate some technical interviews. My answer was hell yeah!
I think it&amp;rsquo;s great that management involves senior developers in the selection process. On the one hand, it&amp;rsquo;s good for the team if they know that someone who is hands-on with the code saw the new colleague, talked to him/her and asked - hopefully - relevant questions. On the other hand, it&amp;rsquo;s also reassuring for the candidates that they can talk to someone who is doing the same job as he would.</description></item><item><title>01 Product of Array Except Self</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/01-product-of-array-except-self-20ak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 06:48:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/01-product-of-array-except-self-20ak/</guid><description>I have been discussing many topics in my blog but it’s time to start from the root once again. In this blog and upcoming few we’ll discuss how to attempt general competitive programming questions, no fancy data structures or algorithms, but thinking outside the box and cooking up some good enough solutions together.
Understanding how code works is more important than coding an app, Understanding how your own thoughts work is even more important.</description></item><item><title>1 line of code How to reverse all words of a string</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-all-words-of-a-string-n26/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 15:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-all-words-of-a-string-n26/</guid><description>1 const reverseWords = (str) =&amp;gt; str.split(&amp;#34; &amp;#34;).map((word) =&amp;gt; [...word].reverse().join(&amp;#34;&amp;#34;)).join(&amp;#34;&amp;#34;); Returns the string with all words reversed
Improved version with unicode support 1 const reverseWords = (str) =&amp;gt; str.replace(/(\p{L}+)/gu, (word) =&amp;gt; [...word].reverse().join(&amp;#39;&amp;#39;)); The repository and npm package You can find the all the utility functions from this series at github.com/martinkr/onelinecode The library is also published to npm as @onelinecode for your convenience.</description></item><item><title>1 line of code How to reverse a string</title><link>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-a-string-2pga/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 14:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.portalsindex.xyz/posts/1-line-of-code-how-to-reverse-a-string-2pga/</guid><description>1 const reverseString = str =&amp;gt; [...str].reverse().join(&amp;#34;&amp;#34;); Returns the reversed string.
The repository &amp;amp;amp; npm package You can find the all the utility functions from this series at github.com/martinkr/onelinecode The library is also published to npm as @onelinecode for your convenience.
The code and the npm package will be updated every time I publish a new article.
Follow me on Twitter: @martinkr and consider to buy me a coffee</description></item></channel></rss>